itsbx.com 2019-06-30

# Boxden.Com - The urban web's front page

Privacy Statement 

Boxden.com values your privacy. Your registration information and any other details you place on our sites are subject to our Privacy Policy. Any and all personal information you provide us will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned to anyone outside Boxden.com.

Members are required to provide their name & email address. Registration requires a valid email address. We delete accounts from users whose emails bounce. 

You have the ability to keep your e-mail address hidden from other users by selecting that option within your user profile. You also decide how much personal information is visible to Boxden members in your user profile. Non-members are not able to see your profile details, email you, or send you a private message. From the User Control Panel, you have the option of providing some additional information such as occupation, interests, and homepage URL. This information is made available to other Boxden users to foster a sense of community. If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave these fields blank. 

Use of the website involve use of "cookies.”. This includes retention of your username and password on the computer you are working on, which helps track your last read message when you revisit the forum. You have the option to turn these cookies off at any time by updating your user profile preferences. We advise you to do so if you use a shared, public or hospital computer, or remember to log out after each session to prevent unauthorized access under your account. If your browser doesn’t support cookies, or if you have cookies turned off, these preferences will not be set. 

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on the visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.  
* You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Google Advertiser features is used; Advertiser Features include Demographics and Interest reporting, Remarketing, GDN Impression Reporting and the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration. You may opt out by following this link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
